♪♪♪
♪ I HAVE THIS THING WHERE I GET
OLDER BUT JUST NEVER WISER ♪
♪ MIDNIGHTS BECOME
MY AFTERNOONS ♪
♪ WHEN MY DEPRESSION WORKS THE
GRAVEYARD SHIFT ♪
♪ ALL OF THE PEOPLE I’VE GHOSTED
STAND THERE IN THE ROOM ♪
♪ I SHOULD NOT BE LEFT TO MY OWN
DEVICES, THEY COME WITH PRICES
AND VICES, I END UP IN CRISIS ♪
♪ TALE AS OLD AS TIME ♪
♪ I WAKE UP SCREAMING FROM
DREAMING ONE DAY I’LL WATCH AS
YOU’RE LEAVING ♪
♪ ‘CAUSE YOU GOT TIRED OF MY
SCHEMING FOR THE LAST TIME ♪
♪ IT’S ME ♪
♪ HI ♪
♪ I’M THE PROBLEM, IT’S ME ♪
♪ AT TEATIME ♪
♪ EVERYBODY AGREES ♪
♪ I’LL STARE DIRECTLY AT THE SUN
BUT NEVER IN THE MIRROR ♪
♪ IT MUST BE EXHAUSTING ALWAYS
ROOTING FOR THE ANTI-HERO ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I FEEL LIKE
EVERYBODY IS A SEXY BABY ♪
♪ AND I’M A MONSTER ON
THE HILL ♪
♪ TOO BIG TO HANG OUT ♪
♪ SLOWLY LURCHING TOWARD YOUR
FAVORITE CITY ♪
♪ PIERCED THROUGH THE HEART BUT
NEVER KILLED ♪
♪ DID YOU HEAR MY COVERT
NARCISSISM I DISGUISE AS ♪
♪ ALTRUISM LIKE SOME KIND
OF CONGRESSMAN ♪
♪ TALE AS OLD AS TIME ♪
♪ I WAKE UP SCREAMING FROM
DREAMING ONE DAY I’LL WATCH AS
YOU’RE LEAVING ♪
♪ AND LIFE WILL LOSE ALL ITS
MEANING FOR THE LAST TIME ♪
♪ IT’S ME ♪
♪ HI ♪
♪ I’M THE PROBLEM, IT’S ME ♪
♪ AT TEATIME ♪
♪ EVERYBODY AGREES ♪
♪ I’LL STARE DIRECTLY AT THE SUN
BUT NEVER IN THE MIRROR ♪
♪ IT MUST BE EXHAUSTING ALWAYS
ROOTING FOR THE ANTI-HERO ♪
♪ I HAVE THIS DREAM MY
DAUGHTER-IN-LAW KILLS ME FOR
THE MONEY ♪
♪ SHE THINKS I LEFT THEM IN
THE WILL ♪
♪ THE FAMILY GATHERS ‘ROUND AND
READS IT ♪
♪ AND THEN SOMEONE SCREAMS OUT ♪
♪ “SHE’S LAUGHING UP AT US
FROM HELL!” ♪
- WHAT?? WHAT DOES IT SAY?
- IT'S THE WORST
- BUT WHO GOT THE BEACH HOUSE!?
- SHE’S HAVING IT TURNED INTO A
CAT SANCTUARY
- WHAT!? CATS DON'T EVEN LIKE
THE BEACH
- WHAT ABOUT THE REST OF
THE ASSETS?
- I FLEW ALL THE WAY HERE
FROM IBIZA
- TO MY CHILDREN,
I LEAVE 13 CENTS.
- CURSES, SCREAMS OF PROTEST.
- WAIT. WAIT. YOU GUYS.
THERE’S PROBABLY A SECRET
ENCODED MESSAGE THAT MEANS
SOMETHING ELSE!
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH THAT'S WHAT
MOM WOULD ALWAYS DO.
“PS: THERE IS NO SECRET
ENCODED MESSAGE THAT MEANS
SOMETHING ELSE. LOVE, TAYLOR”
GREAT, WELL GOOD JOB CHAD.
YOU FINALLY PUSHED IT TOO FAR.
WHAT ARE YOU
IMPLYING BY THAT?
I THINK SHE'S IMPLYING THAT
YOU HAVEN'T HESITATED TO TRADE
ON MOM'S NAME
EXCUSE ME ?
UMMM, DO YOU NOT REMEMBER YOUR
BOOK ‘GROWING UP SWIFT’
AND YOUR STUPID PODCAST 'LIFE
COMES AT YOU SWIFTLY'
WHICH I'M PRETTY SURE YOU ARE
RECORDING FOR ON YOUR PHONE
RIGHT NOW
CHAD, COME ON!
AT HER FUNERAL CHAD
OKAY WELL WHY DON'T YOU GO CRY
ABOUT IT AT THE COUNTRY CLUB
THAT YOU NAME DROPPED MOM TO
GET INTO, PRESTON.
AND KIMBER YOU ARE LITERALLY
WEARING HER CLOTHES RIGHT NOW.
NO, I'M NOT.
THAT’S FROM THE FEARLESS
TOUR, 2009.
OKAY, WELL YOU KNOW WHAT, WE
WERE VERY, VERY CLOSE.
I MISS HER.
THEY WERE SO CLOSE.
OKAY, I'M JUST GONNA SAY IT,
I THINK SHE KILLED HER.
YOU’VE GONE TOO FAR.
KIMBER WAS THE LAST ONE WITH
HER!! SHE DIDN’T FALL OFF THAT
BALCONY!! SHE WAS PUSHED.
NOOOO!!!
YOU MONSTER!!!
♪ IT’S ME ♪
♪ HI ♪
♪ I’M THE PROBLEM, IT’S ME ♪
♪ IT’S ME ♪
♪ HI ♪
♪ I’M THE PROBLEM, IT’S ME ♪
♪ IT’S ME ♪
♪ HI ♪
♪ EVERYBODY AGREES ♪
♪ IT’S ME ♪
♪ HI ♪
♪ I’M THE PROBLEM, IT’S ME ♪
♪ AT TEATIME ♪
♪ EVERYBODY AGREES ♪
♪ I’LL STARE DIRECTLY AT THE SUN
BUT NEVER IN THE MIRROR ♪
♪ IT MUST BE EXHAUSTING ALWAYS
ROOTING FOR THE ANTI-HERO ♪